Edward Dorn Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Submitted Manuscripts, undated
  - Collected Work (K - L), undated (Box 47:, Folder 768)
  - Collected Work (M - Q), undated (Box 47:, Folder 769)
  - Collected Work (R), undated (Box 48:, Folder 770)
  - Collected Work (S - Z), undated (Box 47:, Folder 771)
- Series VI: Broadsides, undated
  - Broadsides Advertisements, undated (Box 28:, Folder 461)
  - Broadsides Art, undated (Box 28:, Folder 462)
  - Broadsides Poetry, undated (Box 28:, Folder 463)
- Series VII: AV Material and Artifacts, undated
  - Behymer Tapes, undated (Box 49)
  - Brakhage Tapes, undated
  - California Videocassette, undated
  - Cockburn & Said Interview, undated
  - Interview of Tom Clark, undated
  - Just Buffalo/Videopoetics Videocassette, undated
  - The Last Words of Hassan-I-Sabbah 45 Record, undated
  - Package of Railway Dust, undated
  - The Party, undated
- Series VIII: Photographs, undated
  - Unidentified Photos (1) (Box 50:, Folder 772)
  - Unidentified Photos (2) (Box 50:, Folder 773)
  - Unidentified Photos (3) (Box 29)
  - Unidentified Woman Photo (Box 50:, Folder 774)
  - Adams Photos (Box 50:, Folder 775)
  - Behymer Photo (1) (Box 50:, Folder 776)
  - Behymer Photos (2) (Box 50:, Folder 777)
  - Bent Photo (Box 50:, Folder 778)
  - Berlin Photo (1) (Box 50:, Folder 779)
  - Berlin Photo (2) (Box 50:, Folder 780)
  - Berlin Photo (3) (Box 50:, Folder 781)
  - Berlin Photo (4) (Box 50:, Folder 782)
  - Berlin Photo (5) (Box 50:, Folder 783)
  - Berlin Photo (6) (Box 50:, Folder 784)
  - Bottoms Photos (Box 50:, Folder 785)
  - Bowering Photo (Box 50:, Folder 786)
  - Buck Photos (1) (Box 50:, Folder 787)
  - Buck Photos (2) (Box 50:, Folder 788)
  - C. T. B. A. Photos (Box 50:, Folder 789)
  - Chandell Photos (Box 50:, Folder 790)
  - Clark Photos (Box 50:, Folder 791)
  - Clark Slide (Box 50:, Folder 792)
  - Creeley Photo (Box 50:, Folder 793)
  - Dawson Photos (Box 50:, Folder 794)
  - Donovan Photo (Box 50:, Folder 795)
  - Doyle Photos (Box 50:, Folder 796)
  - Dunbar Photo (1) (Box 50:, Folder 797)
  - Dunbar Photos (2) (Box 50:, Folder 798)
  - Golding Photo (Box 50:, Folder 799)
  - Goodwin Photos (1) (Box 50:, Folder 800)
  - Goodwin Photos (2) (Box 50:, Folder 801)
  - Goodwin Photos (3) (Box 50:, Folder 802)
  - Handlet Photo (Box 50:, Folder 803)
  - Herald Journal Photo (Box 50:, Folder 804)
  - Innskeep Photos (Box 50:, Folder 805)
  - Kimball Photos (Box 50:, Folder 806)
  - Kitchell Photo (Box 50:, Folder 807)
  - Lacinski Photo (Box 50:, Folder 808)
  - Lytle Photos (Box 50:, Folder 809)
  - MacAdams Photo (Box 50:, Folder 810)
  - Mann Photos (Box 50:, Folder 811)
  - McNaughton Photo (Box 50:, Folder 812)
  - Moritz Photos (Box 50:, Folder 813)
  - Negative Car Picture (Box 50:, Folder 814)
  - Nixon Photo (Box 50:, Folder 815)
  - Notely Photo (Box 50:, Folder 816)
  - Obermayr Photos (Box 50:, Folder 817)
  - Okamura Photo (Box 50:, Folder 818)
  - Pavesic Photo (Box 50:, Folder 819)
  - Prynne Photos (Box 50:, Folder 820)
  - Raworth Photos (1) (Box 50:, Folder 821)
  - Raworth Photos (2) (Box 50:, Folder 822)
  - Raworth Photos (3) (Box 50:, Folder 823)
  - Raworth Photos (4) (Box 50:, Folder 824)
  - Raworth Photos (5) (Box 50:, Folder 825)
  - Raworth Photos (6) (Box 50:, Folder 826)
  - Raworth Photos (7) (Box 50:, Folder 827)
  - Raworth Photos (8) (Box 50:, Folder 828)
  - Raworth Photos (9) (Box 50:, Folder 829)
  - Raworth Photos (10) (Box 50:, Folder 830)
  - Raworth Photos (11) (Box 50:, Folder 831)
  - Raworth Photos (12) (Box 50:, Folder 832)
  - Raworth Photos (13) (Box 50:, Folder 833)
  - Raworth Photos (14) (Box 50:, Folder 834)
  - Ruben Photo (Box 50:, Folder 835)
  - Ruppert Photo (Box 50:, Folder 836)
  - Sanders Photo (Box 50:, Folder 837)
  - Sedgwick Photos (Box 50:, Folder 838)
  - Simmons Photos (Box 50:, Folder 839)
  - Sotomayor Photo (Box 50:, Folder 840)
  - Walsh Photos (Box 50:, Folder 841)
  - Warner Photos (Box 50:, Folder 842)
  - Wedemeyer Photo (Box 50:, Folder 843)
  - Wieners Photos (Box 50:, Folder 844)
  - Young Photo (Box 50:, Folder 845)